

GENÍS GILAVERT BERLANA

Vallparda nº 122-124 ENTLO 2a, Hospitalet de Llobregat, Barcelona 08904

4 93 448 36 23 **609 156 909**

2005

2011

■ anonymousheimer@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Spark Ibérica

Barcelona

Leadership skills, analytic capacity and excellent problem solving skills.

I love mathematics and programming.

I approved two years in the mathematics degree with mention in computing.

After to change of job to computer systems administrator, I stopped the carreer and continued expanding my knowledge with others programming languages.

Currently, I continue working and studying a course of Programming videogames with Unreal and reading a book "Mastering Unreal Engine 4.X" to improve my C++ skills within the Unreal Engine environment.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

EMI LOTMENT HISTORY	
Waiter Bar Oasis - Hospitalet de Llobregat	January 1997 to January 1999
Football referee Federació Catalana de Futbol - Barcelona	January 1998 to January 2004
Bellboy Grupo de Hoteles Gargallo - Barcelona	March 2002 to June 2002
Collaborator Jornadas Internacionales de fisioterapia - Barcelona	October 2004 to October 2004
Commercial Publingenios - Barcelona	November 2004 to January 2005
Administrative Assistant Air France - Tremblay-en-France	January 2005 to September 2005
Network Operator for telefonica Spark Ibérica - Barcelona	October 2005 to December 2005
Soldier in the specialty of transmissions Ministerio de Defensa - Madrid	April 2006 to August 2017
Computer systems administrator Omega Peripherals - Barcelona	May 2017 to working currently
TRAINING	
Federació Catalana de Futbol Camp Barcelona Football referee title: Sports	1998
Institut Eduard Fontserè Hospitalet de Llobregat Baccalaureate title: Technological	2003
Dirección General de Tráfico Barcelona Driving license class B	2003

IT Essentials course: PC Hardware and Software: Computing

Network Operator course: Computing

Acuartelamiento San Fernando

CAMPUS 25 2011 Barcelona

University access certificate

Universitat Pompeu Fabra 2013
Barcelona

Decoding Algebra course: Mathematics

Universitat Autónoma de Barcelona 2017

Barcelona

Course 1 of Design and creation of videogames: Videogames programing

Universitat de Barcelona 2017

Barcelona

Two years in the mathematics degree with mention in computing: Pure mathematics

- subjects of computing degree:
 - Algorísmica
 - Programació II
 - Estructura de dades
 - Dissenv de Software
 - Projecte Integrat de Software

Commvault 2018

New Jersey

Commvault Technical Sales Professional - CVTSP19

Espai 2018

Barcelona

Higher course of development and implementation of web applications

KNOWLEDGES, SKILLS AND APTITUDES

Programming languages

C, C++, Java, Mathematica, Python, PHP and Javascript

Others languages

HTML5, CSS3, jquery, ajax and SQL

Languages

Native: Spanish, Catalan Medium: English

Work platforms

Netbeans AndroidStudio Mathematica Eclipse Microsoft Visual C++ Visual Studio Code

Applications

Videogame: Bubbles math Javascript

competition of web videogames

backup analysis Java

free

Videogame: FlyAway Android

subject "integrated software project"

Multimedia player Java

subject "programing II"

Programming projects

Test web PHP

php final exam

Commercial web HTML5 and CSS3

html final exam

Kangaroo service Java

subject "software design"

movies and series service Java

subject "software design"

Other programs C and C++ various subjects

AWARDS AND ACKNOWLEDGEMENTS

university awards

Qualification of Honor's Registration in the subject "Elements de programació"

other awards

Contest of programming a math videogame in Javascript

individual sports

★ Athletics

1º Classified T cross of "Hospitalet de Llobregat"

1º Classified
▼ trophy "ROBERTO CABREJAS" in the institute "IES EDUARD FONTSERE" (3 km) getting record of less time of the institute

1º Classified T Militar trophy "Trofeo SAN FERNANDO" (5 km)

Between the 100 and 200 of 60 thousand people in the course of the Corte inglés (12km in 41 minute)

in Chess

- 1º Classified T tournament in the institute "IES EDUARD FONTSERE"
- 1º Classified League in the institute "IES EDUARD FONTSERE"
- 1º Classified 🝸 summer tournament in a English school camp

Shot with long weapon

1º Classified T Militar trophy "SAN FERNANDO"

☞ Videogames

1º Classified **?** 2 times in a tournament of "Super Smash Bros"

collective sports

Football

- 1º Classified **Y** Many trophies of league "LAS PLANAS"
- 1º Classified T Champions league "LAS PLANAS"
- 1º Classified T summer tournament played in zone Pedralbes from barcelona

Volleyball

1º Classified T tournament in the institute "IES EDUARD FONTSERE"

☞ Videogames

Diamond level playing "League of Legends"

Between the 10 best players of the world with the champion Heimerdinger in "League of Legends"

1º Classified T tournament of couples playing to "Pro Evolution Soccer"